♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 21=
Governor,
should we send someone to confirm
whether Xu You'an is really dead?
No need. Seeing is believing.
The most important thing now
is to get the Buddha Head
and complete the arms deal.
Then, whether it's Rong Xiaonan
or the Xiaosheng Society,
I won't spare either of them.
The place in the photo should be here.
The Jade Buddha Head is indeed here.
Don't move!
Slow down.
Look at this lousy place you picked.
These branches and rocks are killing me.
Governor Xu,
can you show me the manliness you had
when you hit me yesterday?
I originally thought
you were highly skilled in martial arts.
I didn't expect
that you'd also be a paper tiger.
Without me, the paper tiger,
you couldn't have put on this show.
(Spirit Tablet
of Revered Master Rong Huaiqiu)
Master, this time
I won't run away again.
This time I will accomplish
the revenge I haven't taken before
at any cost.
Rong Xiaonan!
Die!
Sorry.
I cannot escape blame
for Adjutant Sun's death.
Can an apology
bring Yongnian back to life?
Why would you be the one to betray us?
Why does it have to be you?
I pretended to surrender to save you.
Will you believe me?
But I saw Yongnian die in front of me
with my own eyes.
I saw you lead men to dig up Head Rong
and Gu Fengqiu's memorial tomb.
I saw you hand over
the phoenix crown to Du Xiaolin.
Do you still want to deceive me?
Xu Fan has retaken Governor Mansion.
You've been hunted.
We are weak,
and nothing can be done.
Right now, our priority
is to get you out.
Get me out for what?
To run for my life?
After you get out,
first find the real Buddha Head.
The Xiaosheng Society
doesn't want a partner,
but the real Buddha Head.
You know where the real Buddha Head is?
When I found out
that my master is Zhao Shengge,
I guessed where he would hide it.
You mean
Gu Fengqiu?
Everything started because of her.
Perhaps it's related to her.
How do you plan to get me out?
A fake death.
To make Xu Fan stop noticing you.
Xu Fan has put a bounty on my head.
You want to use my head to fool him?
No.
You just need to "die" in front of him.
Then my life
is in your hands.
You do know Xu Fan well,
aware that ordinary tricks
can't fool him.
Otherwise, our plan might have failed.
For someone like him,
he will lower his guard
only if you make him think
he's really succeeded.
You took the phoenix crown.
Will the Xiaosheng Society
get suspicious?
They took the crown's
kingfisher feather phoenix head.
I overheard that it seems to be the key
to opening the Jade Buddha Head.
What they want is not the relics,
but the Feng Mausoleum Treasure Map
hidden inside the Jade Buddha Head.
Feng Mausoleum Treasure Map?
And I found out the Japanese
are behind the Xiaosheng Society.
If that's the case,
we mustn't let the jade Buddha Head
fall into Japanese hands.
Xu Fan left in a hurry last night.
Could it be...
It's Miss Jiang. Go save her.
She has been taken by Xu Fan.
You two, go out first.
Stay back!
I'll blow your head off!
Are you alright?
I'm sorry.
I was so useless.
The Jade Buddha Head
was taken by Xu Fan.
It's not your fault.
We didn't plan thoroughly
and put you in danger.
Xu Fan has already gotten
the Jade Buddha Head.
So our plan must be moved up.
We'll send you to a safe place first.
Wait for us there to meet up.
Then you both much also be careful.
Let's go.
Surround this place!
Don't let them escape!
Yes!
I'll draw them away later.
You look for it.
I know Governor Mansion well.
I'll be fine.
Don't move!
Mr. Rong,
where is Xu You'an?
Didn't he die in front of you?
Governor Xu, you're getting old
and forgetful.
It's fine. With you here, I'm not afraid
we won't get Xu You'an.
Go. Bring Mr. Rong an outfit.
Yes.
Xu You'an won't act impulsively.
He knows what he should do now.
Don't worry.
Xu You'an will definitely
come to save you.
Because you are the only family
he has in this world.
Eight years ago when you first met,
he was called Shitou.
Hurry, help Mr. Rong get changed.
I can't wait to watch this good show.
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪